sup everyone Kamath 1 2 3 4 5 here with
a very special video today now I called
up one of my best buds a little white
suddenly may know him as a wicked for
sokka's like with rock on the ground and
I said hey man wanna do an interview for
my channel I mean we already did one
about a year ago just have one knows so
this is give me my second one with him
so jalloo you wait to get started
absolutely cool cool now first question
I've got to ask I know whenever you walk
out TV show whenever you're done with an
outside you and the entire cast just
sits down from the TV and watches the
episode to see how I ended up what was
like when you watch that's the one for
the rock on the ground for the very
first time with the rest of the cast
alright I walk into this room man and I
hit the door and to this day I will
never forget that screen because
audience which is so blown away oh cool
you should audience does that mean you
wash it with not only people you work
with boss some fans absolutely man so I
gotta add with how popular suck on the
ground is do you still get people coming
up to you nowadays just asking you hey
[ __ ] make the voice of Sonic and Spock
on the ground a couple weeks ago and you
know literally I had all these you know
ten eleven year old kids running up to
me like oh my God is this really his
cool
I bet a bunch of modern flour fans were
to kick your ass have you ever run into
any marks on hand that you would just
use a punch in the face I mean what do
you do with my fans like I understand
you you beat the ass but how do you beat
ass haha it depends on the person and
depends on a and like really I want to
just choke it
well you want to choke them on saucepan
well
Agassi I can't disagree with Julia why
you're one cool dude I gotta ask if
Sonic on the ground was ever coming back
and they announced that a director of a
modern Sonic video game was going to be
the guy directing the new socket learn
series how you feel I got a bit
needlessly I would all be pissed off
you cannot give such grants octagon to a
moth I can and let him try to make
something good it just doesn't that's
what I really want to be like shut off
camera whoop his ass oh ha ha ha I'm
glad you think the way I do Julia why